ge-tracker.com 2019-12-21

# Terms & Conditions - GE Tracker

## Sections defined in this policy

  1. Content
  2. Your use of the GE Tracker website
  3. Accounts, passwords and security
  4. Subscription & refund policy for "Premium" edition
  5. Sponsorship & referral scheme
  6. Links to other websites
  7. Cookie policy
  8. Privacy policy
  9. Questions

This is an agreement made between you and GE Tracker ("we" or "us") our software ("the Software") which is made available to end users at the website www.ge-tracker.com ("the Website", which term shall include any mirror site or future incarnation of such site). The Software shall include any updates or fixes thereof. The Software enables the user to access the Web App section of the Website, in the case of our "Premium" edition, to unlock additional features of the Website (which features will change from time to time).

BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SOFTWARE (WHETHER THE FREE VERSION OR THE "PREMIUM" EDITION) YOU ARE DEEMED TO HAVE ACCEPTED THESE TERMS.

## Content

All text, images, user interfaces, video media, artwork, computer code (including but not limited to HTML, JavaScript, ActionScript and XML) and Cascading Style Sheets (collectively known as "Content"), including but not limited to the design, structure, general "look and feel" of the GE Tracker website, is owned or licensed by or to GE Tracker or one of its wholly-owned subsidiaries, and is protected by various intellectual property and copyright laws.

Except as otherwise declared within these Terms of Use, no part of the GE Tracker website or any website owned by GE Tracker may be copied, reproduced, republished, posted, uploaded, or otherwise duplicated on any other computer, server or website for commercial enterprise, without the prior written consent of GE Tracker or one of its wholly owned subsidiaries.

* * *

## Your use of the GE Tracker website

We grant you the non-exclusive right to use the Software via your GE Tracker account. You are hereby authorised to utilise the Software to access the Web App and its features.

This licence is personal to you and you may not share or sub-licence, assign or dispose of the benefit of this licence or of any part of the Software to any other person save for a transfer of the entire Software retaining no copy of or access to the same by you provided that the terms of this licence are notified to and accepted by the transferee.

You are limited to one account per person, which does not include the use of multiple email addresses to create multiple accounts or bypass the software by use of a proxy service or VPN.

Any breach of the terms of this licence or any termination, suspension or expiry of your user account accessing the Website ("User Account") shall be deemed to automatically revoke the rights granted to you hereunder with immediate effect and without further notice.

We reserve the right to filter traffic and/or disable your account when connecting from certain ISPs and VPN providers.

You must not create an account on GE Tracker if you are under the age of 16.

We reserve all rights not expressly granted hereunder.

### Intellectual property and restricted activities

You may not copy, alter, reverse engineer or disassemble the Software for any purpose, or use the Software to create any other software or publish any specifications designed to enable others to do the same. 

We reserve all right and title in the Software and assert all rights of ownership in the same. To the extent that you, in breach of the above terms or otherwise, make any alterations to or create any derivative works from the Software (including by way of reverse engineering of the same) (collectively, "Derivatives") you agree that we shall own the Derivatives from the date of inception and to the extent that any rights in the Derivatives do not automatically vest in us you hereby assign to us with full title guarantee any residual interest you may have therein. 

You shall not attempt to circumvent any security protocols embodied in the Software or share access of your User Account with any other party. 

You may not use any "robot", "spider", "scraper", "deep-link" or any other program, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy, monitor or reproduce the whole or any part of the GE Tracker website or any Content contained therein, or in any way circumvent the navigational structure of the GE Tracker website or any Content, or to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials not purposely made available through the GE Tracker website and the navigational structure contained therein, including but not limited to attempting to execute any arbitrary computer code not part of the GE Tracker website or systems. GE Tracker reserves the right to bar any such activity and/or ban users or Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses from the GE Tracker website.

You may not attempt to gain unauthorised access to any portion or feature of the GE Tracker website not made specifically available to the general public, or any part of any system connected to the GE Tracker website or to any GE Tracker server, or to any services offered by the GE Tracker website, by hacking, password "mining", or any other illegitimate means. GE Tracker reserves the right to bar any such activity through user blacklisting, IP address blocking or similar methods.

You may not probe, scan or test the security systems or vulnerability of the GE Tracker website or any part of any network connected to the GE Tracker website, nor breach any security, encryption or authentication measures employed on the GE Tracker website or any network connected to the GE Tracker website. You may not attempt in any way to trace any information of any other user of or visitor to the GE Tracker website, except any user information specifically made public by that user in any part of the GE Tracker website. This includes any user account on the GE Tracker user database or any other account created on the GE Tracker website not owned by you. You may not use any part of the GE Tracker website to retrieve or attempt to retrieve any personal information pertaining to any user of or visitor to the GE Tracker website, other than your own, except that information which is specifically made public by that user.

* * *

## Accounts, passwords and security

Some features of the GE Tracker website or services offered thereon may require you to register a user account (including registering a user ID and a password). You are entirely responsible for maintaining the security of your account details, including your username and password, and for all activity that occurs under your account. You agree to notify GE Tracker immediately of any unauthorised activity or use of your account or password, or any other breach of your account's security. However, you may be held liable for any loss incurred by GE Tracker or any other user of or visitor to the GE Tracker website due to unauthorised use of your user account.

You may not use anyone else's GE Tracker user account or password at any time without the express permission and consent of said account owner, and only for use permitted by these Terms of Use. GE Tracker cannot and will not be held liable for any loss of damage incurred by your failure to comply with these obligations.

You are solely responsible for all activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify GE Tracker immediately via email upon learning of any unauthorized use of your account, GE Tracker's services, or any other breach of security.

You may request to delete your GE Tracker account by contacting [support@ge-tracker.com](mailto:support@ge-tracker.com). Your IP address information will be stored for 3 months after the deletion of your account, to prevent that IP address being used to create additional accounts and receiving a free trial. IP information will be deleted daily until it has all been purged.

* * *

## Subscription & refund policy for "Premium" edition

If you wish to subscribe to our "Premium" edition of the Software you agree to pay to us a monthly subscription fee in accordance with our payment procedures, whereupon this licence shall extend to the use of the "Premium" edition for so long as you subscribe. 

You may cancel your subscription at any time whereupon this licence shall extend only to the free version of the Software. You are responsible for managing your own subscription, and for security purposes, it is not the responsibility of Staff to cancel on your behalf. 

If the "Premium" edition of the Software fails to function properly due to a defect therein or as a result of any matter affecting the Website and/or your User Account during the period of ten (10) working days following your initial subscription then unless we are able to provide a fix within 24 hours you shall be entitled to cancel your subscription and apply for a full refund of your initial subscription. 

Save as specified in the above clause, all subscription payments are non-refundable. In the event that the Software is discontinued for any reason we will notify you via your User Account and it will be your responsibility to cancel your subscription payments. 

* * *

## Sponsorship & referral scheme

If you wish to join the GE Tracker referral scheme, you may do so by submitting an application. You agree to a 25% fee of profit generated by referred subscriptions only. As the amount of referrals grows, your referral fee will increase, as detailed when your application has been accepted. 

If a user unsubscribes during their subscription period, you will still receive payment for this duration. 

We are not responsible for calculation errors displayed on the My Account - Referrals page. 

We send referral payments no earlier than the 28th of each month via TransferWise to a bank account that you specify. We are not responsible for a delay in receiving payment caused by your banking institution. You retain the option to receive payments via PayPal to a PayPal address you specify.

If you join the referral scheme and have already referred subscribers then you will not be backdated payment. 

You are bound by the terms stated in this 'Sponsorship & Referral Scheme' agreement.

* * *

## Links to other websites

The GE Tracker website may contain hyperlinks to other independent third-party websites ("Linked Sites"). These Linked Sites are provided solely as a convenience to GE Tracker website users or visitors. Such Linked Sites are not affiliated with GE Tracker and thus are outside GE Tracker's control: GE Tracker therefore takes no responsibility for the content contained in any Linked Sites, and does not endorse any content or activity related to such Linked Sites, including but not limited to any information or materials contained therein. Your interaction with any Linked Sites is entirely independent of GE Tracker.

* * *

## Cookie policy

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Cookies are required to use the GE Tracker service.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. 

We use cookies on the Software to identify your browser as a means to provide a better experience to the end user, and to ensure that your browser is not used for account sharing (as detailed in 'Intellectual property and restricted activities'). 

* * *

## Privacy policy

Your privacy is a priority at GE Tracker and we go to great lengths to protect it. We will not pass on your personal details to any third party (unless we are required to by law), nor will we sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, in order for us to offer our services to our users; to enhance the quality of its service from time to time; and to protect the interests of our users, we will in limited circumstances and as further described in this policy, share some of your information with third parties under strict restrictions.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may be served from our third party advertiser, you can view their [privacy policy](https://www.network-n.com/network-privacy-policy/) and [cookie policy](https://www.network-n.com/network-cookie-policy/) here. You can manage your cookies here.

We use Google Analytics and Comscore to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics and Comscore gather information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Comscore's privacy policy is available at <https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy>.

### Why we collect Personal Information

We collect your Personal Information for the purpose of providing you with (and administering) the use of our Websites, products and/or services, whether we do so for payment or free of charge. Your Personal Information also enables us to respond to specific requests that you have made, and to improve the way that we operate and what we offer.

In addition, your Personal Information helps us contact you and keep you updated on any announcements that we think are relevant to you.

Announcements include product and service updates, news and announcements about GE Tracker and its partners. Announcements may also be alerts and notifications sent to you as part of the service we provide when alerting you about events concerning your website.

Your IP address is used in our anti-trial abuse system to prevent users creating multiple accounts to make use of the free trial. We keep website server logs to maintain the security of the website.

### What Personal Information we collect

Upon registration with GE Tracker for a user account you are required to provide the following information: your username, email address and a secure password that only you know. You may optionally provide your personal phone number in the GE Tracker User Account area.

Your browser's User Agent is collected to ensure the best experience when using the website.

IP address is also collected in multiple instances including but not limited to the website activity log, internal advert impressions and email events.

### How do we protect your information?

All credit card information and transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed by our servers. 

We use regular malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. 

We encrypt specific pieces of data to protect the majority of personal data in the event of a data breach. All encrypted values are encrypted using OpenSSL and the AES-256-CBC cipher. Furthermore, all encrypted values are signed with a message authentication code (MAC) to detect any modifications to the encrypted string.

Passwords are encrypted with [bcrypt](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bcrypt).

* * *

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy policy should be addressed to [james@ge-tracker.com](mailto:james@ge-tracker.com).
